[Music]
I'm on a mission to find the ultimate
goal of my fellow Filipinos and we are
here to help them achieve their dreams
who's on our list
help me look for someone whose priority
is to provide the best protection family
and the best retirement plan
number two we need to look for someone
and goal McGraw and Canyon
wealthin na health is well
and last but not the least my business
owners or entrepreneurs
from Sudden shifts in the economy
foreign
[Music]
excuse me excuse me
what's your name is
about personal goals and dreams
[Music]
34 years old I'm married with two kids
and my name is Ayan I'm Andy I'm 45
years old I'm Pat 22 years old
or occupation I own a restaurant and a
wine bar yoga instructor I'm a software
developer freelancer
um
first groceries for this month
ways on how to improve my business
processes
option to customize your plans depends
Nothing in life we can increase our
coverage and Target other life goals
their insurance plans now that have
living benefits
[Music]
well you're still alive and kicking we
can increase your critical illness
benefits
life savings and Investments won't be
exhausted
we have trusted credible and competent
financial advisors that can help secure
your future actually my insurance
and I'm really happy with it um
foreign
[Music]
and bonuses with options to withdraw in
case of family emergency
about five years from now foreign
health and wealth maker
manual life has plants that match your
needs flex your health coverage for as
low as 1000 Pesos monthly
my coverage for cancer
heart attack stroke and over 100 other
dreaded diseases
you can invest and grow your money over
time through different investment funds
make a samatan hospitalization benefits
for only 2 600 pesos monthly
well Sanam franchise
employees we learn as we go along and I
think that's the first step to anything
amen for you Andy negustomnia protect
and business at insuring employees
businessmaker May affordable plans that
can give your employees additional
benefits like Life protection
hospitalization coverage and financial
assistance para happy employees happy
business
talk to a financial advisor scan this to
set an appointment
where do I see myself five years from
now where do you see yourself five years
from now
hey what a fulfilling day Target spotted
I'm optimistic now soon goes achieve
narend now that we have shared with them
what they can do to achieve their goals
I say mission accomplished thank you to
Manulife for letting me do this
and Manulife is here
but for now I'm adding Mission possible
Mission unlock na bye
thank you
[Music]